Unhappy to see you again.
The Addams Family 2 is a animation, family,
comedy film directed by Greg Tiernan.
The Addams get tangled up in more wacky adventures and find themselves involved
in hilarious run-ins with all sorts of unsuspecting characters.
Gomez Addams (voice), played by Oscar Isaac.
Morticia Addams (voice), played by Charlize Theron.
Wednesday Addams (voice), played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Pugsley Addams (voice), played by Javon Walton.
Uncle Fester (voice), played by Nick Kroll.
Cousin Itt (voice), played by Snoop Dogg.
The Addams Family 2 (also known as The Addams Family 2: Road Trip) is a 2021 animated supernatural black comedy
film based on the characters created by Charles Addams and the sequel to The Addams Family (2019).
It was directed by Greg Tiernan and Conrad Vernon and co-directed by Laura Brousseau and Kevin Pavlovic, from a
screenplay by Dan Hernandez, Benji Samit, Ben Queen, and Susanna Fogel, and a story by Hernandez and Samit.
The film stars the voices of Oscar Isaac, Charlize Theron, Chloë Grace Moretz, Nick
Kroll, Javon Walton, Wallace Shawn, Snoop Dogg, Bette Midler, and Bill Hader.
It tells the story of the Addams family as they go on a road trip.
The film was theatrically released in the United States by United Artists Releasing on October 1,
2021, followed by an international release by Universal Pictures on October 8.
It also became available for online rental on the same
day in the United States and Canada.
The film was not as successful as its predecessor and received generally
negative reviews from critics, who criticized the humor and story.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, supernatural,
grand canyon, niagara falls, family.
The tone is lighthearted.